this problem
asks us to use the hash each method
to iterate over our numbers hash and
print both the key and value from each
key value
pair
so we'll call the hash each method on
our hash
and define our block now you may be
wondering how we're going to access
both the key and the value within our
block
the hash each method allows us to define
two block parameters
as we iterate through the hash each key
value pair will be passed to the block
the key will be assigned to the first
block parameter
while the value will be assigned to the
second
and in this simple example we've named
the block parameters to reflect that
so according to the problem description
as we iterate through this hash we want
to output
each key value pair
so we'll invoke put us
and use string interpolation
output each key and each value as part
of a string
now let's run our code and see if our
output matches the expected output that
we were given
and it does